(Sheldon:)Leonard, please,
you know Amy moving in...
(Sheldon:)...marks a level of intimacy
our relationship isn't ready for.
(Penny:)Yes. That is a real thing. And it doesn't
mean you don't care about each other...
(Penny:)...it just means things are moving at a pace
you're not comfortable with. And that's fine.
If he doesn't wanna live with her,
he should tell her how he feels.
(Penny:)Maybe he doesn't know how to say it
without hurting her feelings.
Feelings? Who am I,
a hippie at a love-in? No.
(Sheldon:)The problem is she laid out a series
of logical arguments that I couldn't refute.
- That is the worst, isn't it?
- Yes.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, Sheldon. I can't help you.
Oh, spoiler alert:
This door's about to slam in your face.
(Amy:)Oh, there you are.
When do I get a key to our apartment?
(Leonard:)Um...